<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<versionInfo>
  <id>B2</id>
  <download><![CDATA[http://browserchooser2.com/app/Browser Chooser 2.exe]]></download>
  <releaseinfo>https://bitbucket.org/gmyx/browserchooser2/wiki/Beta2</releaseinfo>
  <details>
    ************************************************************
    *** Please download manually                             ***
    *** http://browserchooser2.com/app/Browser Chooser 2.exe ***
    ************************************************************

    New source code location: https://bitbucket.org/gmyx/browserchooser2
    New web site: http://browserchooser2.com
    p.s. I know it does not look great, but drop me a line if you want to improve it.

    New Features:
    * Better support for Windows 10 and it's variants (e.g. surface)
    * Many lesser known browsers added to browser detection
    * MS Edge properly detected and added
    * Many UI customization have been added, including:
    * change size of icons
    * change spacing of icons
    * starting position
    * can specify a user agent (default is a generic Mozilla string)
    * added chosen browser icons to list of add/edit browsers
    * can turn off downloading of detections files and update checks
    * note: it was downloaded only on first run or if you hit the detect browser button
    * command line options added to bring you to a specified settings page

    Fixed Issues from previous versions:
    * Issue #1: Crash on Win10 open defaults dialog - api has changed in Windows 10
    * Issue #3: Does not properly detect edge / support launching edge
    * Issue #4: Crash on exit. Some systems did not like the way BC2 was exiting. Cleaned up.
    * Issue #5: URL de-shortening could cause wierd URLs to be returned (Facebook). Now sending a user agent string
    * And more crashes.

    Special Thanks for new features
    * J. Scott Elblein: Found many bugs and commiting some code and ui improvements.
    * _pi for many UI suggestions
    * Norbert T. for raising issues and creative use of the tool!
    * Mitch Geller, sakima, bshamster1, johnlgalt, Paul Trevino, Mark Williams for windows 10 / edge information and testing.
    * Everyone who uses this tool and the many creative ways you use it!!
    * If I missed your suggestion, apologies and thanks!

    The documentation (https://bitbucket.org/gmyx/browserchooser2/wiki/Documentation) has been increased. While not yet complete it is covering the main screen and the configuration screen. The add / edit screens will be added later.

    Special thanks to all for testing and proving great feedback!
  </details>
</versionInfo>
